<resources>
    <string name="app_name">List View Test</string>
    <string-array name="dist">

        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Khulna</item>
        <item>Gazipur</item>

        <item>Noakhali</item>
        <item>Chittagong</item>
        <item>Chuadanga</item>

        <item>Faridpur</item>
        <item>Fani</item>

        <item>Commila</item>
        <item>you</item>


    </string-array>

    <string name="Dhaka">Dhaka District (???? ????, Dhaka Jela also Dhaka Zila) is a district located in central Bangladesh,
        and is the densest district in the nation. It is a part of the Dhaka Division. Dhaka, the capital of Bangladesh,
        rests on the eastern banks of the Buriganga River which flows from the Turag to the south of the district.
        While Dhaka (city corporation) occupies only about a fifth of the area of Dhaka district, it is the economic,
        political and cultural centre of the district and the country as a whole. Dhaka District is an administrative entity,
        and like many other cities, it does not cover the modern conurbation which is Greater Dhaka,
        which has spilled into neighbouring districts,
        nor does the conurbation cover the whole district, as there are rural
        areas within the district.
    \n\n
        Profile :\n\n
    Dhaka district was established in 1772. The district consists of 5 upazilas,
        21 thanas, 3 municipalities, 77 union parishads, 1020 mouzas, 1863 villages.\n\n
        Upazilas :\n\n
    Badda Thana, Cantonment Thana, Demra Thana, Dhamrai Upazila,
        Dhanmondi Thana, Dohar Upazila, Gulshan Thana, Hazaribagh Thana,
        Kafrul Thana, Kamrangir Char Thana, Keraniganj Upazila, Khilgaon Thana,
        Kotwali Thana, Lalbagh Thana, Mirpur Thana, Mohammadpur Thana, Motijheel Thana,
        Nawabganj Upazila, Pallabi Thana, Ramna Thana, Sabujbagh Thana, Savar Upazila, Shyampur Thana,
        Sutrapur Thana, Tejgaon Thana, Uttara Thana.
        \n\n
    History :\n\n
        Once upon a time Dhaka was ruled by the Hindu Kings. The Pala and the Sena dynasties ruled Dhaka for many years.
        It was not until early fourteenth century when the Muslim rulers began to come to Bengal.
        Dhaka was made the capital of Bengal in 1608 and Islam Khan renamed Dhaka as Jahangirnagar after
        the name of Emperor Jahangir. In the eighteenth century Dhaka lost political
        importance when Murshid Quli Khan transferred the
        capital of Bengal from Dhaka to Murshidabad. But Dhaka never lost its commercial importance.


    </string>

    <string name="khulna">
        Historical events About 600 years ago Pir (saint) Khan Jahan Ali came to
        this district to preach Islam. He, for the first time, established settlements in the
        Sundarnbans area and established his control over the region having his seat in Bagerhat.
        Mahatma Gandhi visited Khalishpur of the district to invigorate Swadeshi Movement.
        \n\n

Marks of the War of Liberation Mass killing site 3;
        memorial monument 5, memorial sculpture 1 (Bir Bangali).
        \n\n

Literacy rate and educational institutions Average literacy 57.81%; male 63.26%,
        female 51.83% Educational institutions: university 6, medical college 1,
        homeopathic college 1, college 27, art college 1, polytechnic institute 6,
        secondary school 50. Noted educational institutions: khulna university of engineering and
        technology (1969), university of khulna (1991), Khulna Medical College (1992),
        Khulna Homeopathic Medical College, Darul Ihsan University (1989), Asian University of Bangladesh (1996),
        Azam Khan Commerce College, Brajalal College, Government Pioneer Mahila College, Government Sundarban Adarsha College (1969),
        Kopotakkho College (1984), Zobeda Khanam Mahila Degree College (1996), Hazi Mohammad Mohsin College,
        Khulna City Corporation Collegiate School, Khulna Zila School (1885), St. Joseph's High School,
        Coronation Government Secondary School, Tutpara Model Government Primary School (1896),
        Koyra Madinabad High School, Sundarban Secondary School,
        Victoria Infant Primary School, Khulna Alia Madrasa.
    </string>

</resources>
